Xiaoting Tang (Jason)

CONTACT

INFORMATION Apt 104, 395 Angell Street

Providence, Rhode Island, 02906

Work: +1-201-3591019

E-mail: tang_xiaoting@brown.edu

xtt.jsn@gmail.com

HomePage: xttjsn.github.io

RESEARCH INTERESTS **Software Security :** Software Reverse Engineering, Anti-cheating & bypassing, Kernel security and other software securities topics.

PUBLICATION

Xiaoting Tang, Cong Wang, Xingliang Yuan, and Qian Wang, "Non-Interactive Privacy-Preserving Truth Discovery in Crowd Sensing Applications", In the 37th International Conference on Computer Communications (**INFOCOM'18**), Honolulu, HI, USA, 2018. (Acceptance ratio: 309/1606 = 19.2%)

Yifeng Zheng, Huayi Duan, **Xiaoting Tang**, Cong Wang, and Jiantao Zhou, "Denoising in the Dark: Privacy-Assured Healthcare Monitoring with Encrypted Denoising", In the 5th Annual Trends in Forensic Sciences Conference (**TIFS'18**), University of Windsor, ON, Canada, 2018.

SOFTWARES

GASH - GArbled Circuit SyntHesizer – a self-contained framework for secure multi-party computation using Yao's garbled circuit written in C++. Softwares includes a language parser and circuit execution framework. Link

GAHS-viewer - A user-friendly front-end for GASH. Developed for MacOS. Link (use the gash-gui branch)

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE **Research Assistant**, City University of Hong Kong

August 2016 - Dec 2017

• Machine Learning over Hybrid Data: Secure Realization and Acceleration

- Propose a new method to improve privacy-perserving machine leanning system's performance
- Provide adjustable trade-off for users with both security and performance requirements
- Improve existing framework by adopting more efficient algorithms for garbled circuit
- Non-Interactive Privacy Preserving Truth Discovery
 - Completely remove the online requirement of server and clients during protocol execution
 - Failure resistance during client's submission of information
 - Has comparable and practical performance compared with prior arts
- . Verifiable Middlebox Service
 - Develop a modular router system using Click language
 - Implement Ringer a middlebox fraud detection mechanism
 - Conduct systematic testing of current system

PREVIOUS EMPLOYMENT

Senior Developer, Accord Apps Development and Marketing

June 2015 to May 2016

- Selected Apps:
 - Smartrate High Volume Currency Exchange, 3000 downloads in 3 months
 - Smartguy Real Time Photo Retouching, 1200 downloads in 1 month
 - JinQing Registering System for JingQing Volunteering Organization
 - Mitsubishi Full Catelogue System for Mistsuishi Asia Inc.
- Comments:

Ting is the best intern I have ever had. - Mr. Jason Chong, President

Industrial Trainee, HSBC Hong Kong

June 2014 to Dec 2014

Finance IT Department, ShekMun

- Supervisor: Mr. Robin Kong
- Automatic Transaction System Stability Examination
- · Advancement in Annual Reporting System

EDUCATION

M.S., Computer Science, Brown University

Jan. 2018 - Present

- Core Courses:
 - CS1670 Operating System by Prof. Tom W. Doeppner: A
 - CS1510 Cryptography by Prof. Anna Lysyanskaya: A
- CGPA: 4.0

B.S., Computer Science, City University of Hong Kong

Sep. 2012 - Feb. 2017

- Honored Degree
- Core Courses: Data Structures, Design and Analysis of Algorithms, Operating System, Software Design, Machine Learning, Internet Application Programming, Computer Networks, Computer Organizations, Database Systems
- CGPA: 3.18

PROJECTS EXPERIENCE

• Return-to-libc attack on Linux x86

Apr 2018

SELF-CONDUCTED PROJECT

Brown University, Providence

- Bypass non-executable stack using return address in libc.so
- Keywords: Binary exploitation, buffer overflow
- Stack smash attack on Linux x86

Apr 2018

SELF-CONDUCTED PROJECT

Brown University, Providence

- · Gain root via stack overflow on a program marked setuid
- Keywords: Binary exploitation, buffer overflow
- VFS (Virtual File System)

Apr 2018

COURSE PROJECT

Brown University, Providence

- Weenix (Unix-like OS) virtual file system
- Keywords: File System

• Mthread Apr 2018

COURSE PROJECT

Brown University, Providence

- User-level multi-threading library backed by multiple LWP (Light Weight Process)
- Keywords: Multi-threading

• Uthread Apr 2018

COURSE PROJECT

Brown University, Providence

Brown University, Providence

- User-level multi-threading library backed by one LWP (Light Weight Process)
- Keywords: Multi-threading
- Gash GArbled SyntHesizer (for secure multi-party computation)

Apr 2018

RESEARCH PROJECT

- Compile c-like function to binary circuit in AIG(And-Inverter Graph)-like format
- Execute Yao's protocol on fixed-key AES
- Support 64-bit value
- See www.github.com/xttjsn/gash for details
- Keywords: Garbled Circuit, Circuit Compilation

Nov 2016 • Autonomous Evolution: Deep Reinforcement Learning in Simulated Car Test SELF-CONDUCTED PROJECT CityU, HK • Implement a Deep Q-learning Network • Build simulation with real world physics system using Box-2D • Keywords: Reinforcement learning, DON, Autonomous Car, Simulation Test, Game AI, Box-2D • Mobile Multi-Digit Inference System Sep - Nov 2016 SELF-CONDUCTED PROJECT CityU, HK · Design individual loss function for each digit and digit length • Build a mobile app with live inference capability • Organize 18 convolutional and dense layers • Keywords: Deep Neural Network, Multi-Digit Prediction, Mobile App, Tensorflow • Learn By Failure: Tic Tac Toe AI Nov 2016 SELF-CONDUCTED PROJECT CityU, HK • Implementing Q-learning algorithms • Design an recursive function to explore all game states within O(n)• Develop both CMD and GUI interface • Keywords: Q-learning, MDP, Reinforcement Learning, Game AI, PyGame • Kaggle Comp: High Dimensional Prediction With Anonymous Feature Oct - Nov 2016 COURSE PROJECT CityU, HK • Use Gradient Boosting to handle high dimensional data · Visualize gradient distribution • Keywords: Supervised Learning, Regression, Gradient Boosting, Feature Anonymity • Kaggle Comp: Airline Tweet Sentimental Analysis Oct 2016 COURSE PROJECT CityU, HK • Top 3 in accuracy • Design a robust preprocessing system • Combine KPCA and LinearSVM • **Keywords:** Supervised Learning, Text Classification, Sentimental Analysis • Kaggle Comp: Movie Similarity Analysis With Auto Feature Selection Oct 2016 COURSE PROJECT CityU, HK • Top 2 in accuracy • Maximize feature usage by adding word embeddings • Use pair-wise Euclidean distance • Keywords: Unsupervised Learning, Similarity Analysis, Word Embedding • Titanic Passenger Survival Prediction Sep 2016 COURSE PROJECT CityU, HK • Use optimzed random forest • Use hand-crafted decision tree for interpretation

• **Keywords:** Supervised Learning, Classification, Decision Tree

Self-Drive Cab AI Design				Sep 2016
SELF-CONDUCTED PROJECT			CityU, HK	
 Implement Q-learning for optim State interpretation: safer than for Build GUI for game Keywords: Q-learning, Reinfor Discrete Policy Inference 	aster		me,	
• Novel Author Authenticity Discrim	ination			Jul 2016
SELF-CONDUCTED PROJECT				CityU, HK
 Propose Habit of Auxliary Word Solve a historical question of Di Keywords: Cross Validation, St Term Frequency - Inverse Document 	<i>reams in R</i> upervised	Red Mansion Learning, Wor	rd Count,	
OldCR - Training OCR For Old Book Scans				May 2016
Final Year Project			CityU, HK	
 Propose Manufacture Dataset w Pixel level image manipulation Keywords: sklearn, Python Ima Active Learning 				
• Evolution - A Simple yet Additive (Game			Mar 2016
SELF-CONDUCTED PROJECT			CityU, HK	
 Simple rule - two elements com Big database of 350 elements Keywords: 2D Game, PyGame 				
• Playing Music Without Instrument - Magic Glove				Jul 2015
INTEL CUP UNDERGRADUATE DESIGN CONTEST				SJTU, Shanghai
 Top 3 among 50 candidates Use gyroscope and acceleromete Keywords: Arduino, Manufacto 		U 1	tion	
• Freeze Frame - Extreme Environment Research in Antarctica			Dec 2014	
EXPEDITION & EXHIBITION			CityU, HK	
 Construct 3D model from photo Address Environmental Issues: I global warming Keywords: Science as Art, Vert 3D Modelling 	Drifting g		g,	
Computer Language Machine Learning Game Tech	C++ sklearn Unreal	Python Tensorflow	Keras	

TECHNICAL STRENGTHS

Involvement	• Weekly sharer of CUPA(CityU Postgraduate Association) Reading Club	2016 - Present
	 Co-editor of CodingPy (A local digital technical magazine on Python) 	2016 - Present
	Member of Hong Kong Mountain Climbing Club	2014 - Present
	Committee of Mainland Student Association, City University of Hong Kong	g 2012 - 2014
	• Tutor and Ambassador of CityU Empowerment Project (Education service for students with disabilities)	2012 - 2014
Awards	• Dean's List, City University of Hong Kong	2012 - 2013
	Best Project, Antarctica Expedition Exhibition Award	2014
	• 3rd Prize, Intel Embedded System Competition	2014
	Fellowship in CityU Mainland Excellent Students	2012 - 2015
	Trailwalker Award - Oxfam Trailwalker Hong Kong	2016
	Cycler Award - Cycle For Millions, ShangCom Bank, Hong Kong	2016
More Information	More information can be found at http://xttjsn.github.io/.	